Alireza Kavian

C.E.O at Brilacasck

Website: https://alireza-kavian.github.io
Email: alireza.kavian7@gmail.com

Also known as @alireza_kay or @alirezakay on social networks.

So far, I've passed 3 years of university.

In free times, I do learn more about my favourite fields like web development, User Interface/Experience and researching the relevant issues.

I gained experience through various projects of University in several fields of #CE My major skill is on **front-end** development.

To know more about my works, take a look at my linkedin and brilacasck corp.

I'd like to expand my experiences, every day :)

Also to study at the 'University Of Toronto' in Canada OR' ETH Zurich' in switzerland some day

Experience

C.E.O at Brilacasck

JULY 2017 - PRESENT

Chief Execution Officer

Brilacasck

In 2017 I founded this company alongside with my friend @soheilch.

To gain more experience, we've done diverse projects in different fields of our courses together in university.

Then after a year with another friend ours (@amirhkh), we did extend our team.

After that we are a young small team with full of creativity and incentives.

A self-employed organization working in the way of **Agile development.**

Developer Internship at Ysorkh

JULY 2018 - PRESENT

Developer

Ysorkh

I've got my internship in some fields of **Network/Web Security**, **Web SEO** and **Professional Web Development** for deciding what would be the best to concentrate on.

Education

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

2015 - PRESENT

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering,

In 2015, I got entered to the university with great inducements for progressing Till now my total average grade has been: **18.43** (of 20)

KNTU University In Tehran, Iran

Skills

Global Skills

- Scrum Project Management
- Team Management
- Idea Performer
- Teaching
- Soccer (GoalKeeping | Defending)
- Ping-Pong

Programming

- Industry Knowledge
 - Front-End Development
 - Web Development
 - Software Engineering
 - AVR Programming
 - PhotoShop
 - o 3D Max
 - Microsoft Office (powerpoint word excel)
 - o Agile Developing

Tools And Technologies

- Javascript
- o CSS
- Linux
- HTML
- IQuery
- ReactJS
- AngularJS
- Bootstrap
- o PHP
- SQL
- Python
- 。 C
- o C++
- Intel X86 Assembly (NASM)
- AVR Assembly
- Android
- VHDL

Certifications

Web Designing (Front-End)

NOVEMBER 2017

University Of Tehran

Most concentrate on **html** / **css** / **javascript** / **jquery**

Volunteerings

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

OCTOBOR 2017 TO JANUARY

Science And Technology

Role: **Undergraduate Teaching Assistant**Course: Theory of Language and Automaton

Professor: Dr. S.H. Khaasteh

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

FEBRUARY 2018 TO JUNE 2018

Science And Technology

Role: Undergraduate Teaching Assistant

Course: Compiler

Professor: Dr. S. Sedighian Kashi.

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

FEBRUARY 2018 TO JUNE 2018

Science And Technology

Role: Undergraduate Teaching Assistant

Course: Assembly Language (x86 Intel assembly language)

Professor: Dr. B. Nasihatkon

Projects

Simulating A Simple Text Editor With C Language

TERM 1 - 2015

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term1

With using c / c++ language and also BGI graphical library for my first main programming major project

Simulating Graphical Plant Grwoth With Java

TERM 2 - 2016

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term2

Using OOP (object oriented programming) in java Language and also graphical java framework JavaFX

Implementing DFS/BFS Algorithms With

TERM 2 - 2016

Java

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term2

Using java / javaFX to commit this algorithms to an non-directed graph

Implementing A Simple Java Parser With Java Language

TERM 3 - 2016

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term3

A simple compiler for java language for detecting typical errors using CFG (context free grammars) and CYK algorithm.

Implemented with java language

Implementing A Graphical Chess Game WithJava

TERM 4 - 2017

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term4

A nearly pleasant graphical chess game implemented with java language and using JavaFX & JavaAWT.

Algorithms: min-max-tree & alpha-beta-game-tree

Simulating A Plenary CPU Using MIPS Concepts With VHDL

TERM 4 - 2017

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term4

A MIPS-like processor implemented in VHDL language. (RISC CPU) $\,$

Creating A Full Compiler With Java

TERM 5 - 2017

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term5

Using compiler concepts to create a complete compiler for parsing any languages you want to invent.

Using java / JavaFX

Creating An Online Shopping Website Using MySQL And PHP

TERM 5 - 2017

https://alirezakay.github.io/showcase/term5

A website like: digikala

implemented for the course 'Database' With PHP, MySQL, Apache, Bootstrap

Simulating Micro Processor Communication With SystemC Language

TERM 6-2018

https://alirezakay.github.io/term6

Communication between micro-processor and accelerator with shared memory in a bus context.

Using SystemC language for hardware-software co-design simulation

Created using Resumonk - Online Resume Builder

Tiny Courseware System For Computer Engineers (TCS4CE)

MARCH 2018 TO JUNE 2018

https://alirezakay.github.io/term6

This project was going to be implemented for the course **Software Engineering** on aweb context.

I started implementation alongside my two other **team mates**. a trio team.

It was a good chance to expose the result of this project to the authorities of our college.

This project is a system for creating courses by teachers / compiling and running codes by students and get score at the same moment.

a handy courseware.

Languages

Persian (Native), **English** (Professional working proficiency), **Arabic** (Limited working proficiency)